ADEM SEHIRGEL

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

As a graduate from an International Business school, valuable experience has been gained working in various industries. Curiosity and passion for web development led to learning full-stack technologies. During the previous year, dedication was directed towards delivering consulting and management services as an independent professional.

WORK HISTORY

Management Consultant, 04/2023 to Current Capnova Consulting & Management - London

- · Research possible organisational improvements.
- Observe systems and staff operations throughout organisation, compiling current and accurate information.
- Resolved conflicts and negotiated mutually beneficial agreements between parties.
- Managed over 50 customer calls per day to help organisations improve customer satisfaction and achieve measurable results.

SELF EMPLOYED, 01/2018 to 03/2023 London City Pedicab & Delivery - London, UK

- Completed customer orders with speed and accuracy.
- · Worked flexible hours, covering nights, weekends and bank holidays.
- · Carried out day-to-day duties accurately and efficiently.
- · Increased customer satisfaction by resolving issues.

VOLUNTEER, 06/2018 to 12/2018

Oxfam - London, UK

- · Monitored and updated stock levels and inventory databases.
- Quickly learned and applied new skills to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- · Processed invoices and payment runs with complete accuracy.
- · Applied positive customer service approach to increase satisfaction levels.

TEAM MEMBER, 05/2016 to 09/2016

Massanutten - Virginia, USA

- Prepared and packaged orders with precise presentation skills.
- · Offered exceptional customer service with strong product knowledge.
- Used initiative to foresee customer and team needs, taking preventative action to minimise issues.
- Promoted continuous improvement by problem-solving and sharing suggestions to optimise team operations.

OPERATIONS TEAM MEMBER, 01/2016 to 05/2016

DHL Express - Istanbul, TR

- · Completed work following safety rules for best working practices.
- Picked, packed and dispatched high-volume orders, consistently exceeding warehouse performance targets.

CONTACT

Address: 6 Risborough Close, London, UK N10 3PL

Phone: +447897602936

Email: ademsehirgel@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- PHP
- React
- Redux
- Bootstrap
- · Marketing and sales consulting
- · Business planning
- Leadership
- · Problem-solving
- · Customer-focused
- Management

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Business Administration, International Business & Economics -Distinction, 09/2012 to 01/2017 Mehmet Akif Ersoy University - Turkey

Higher National Diploma, Electronic Technologies - Distinction, 09/2006 to 06/2010

Kayseri Technical School - Turkey

LANGUAGES

English

Fluent

Turkish

Native

Spanish

Elementary

- Monitored crowd to proactively identify problems and keep groups under control.
- Reported issues and damages to senior warehouse staff, enabling prompt, effective resolutions.